<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>A Tract Profile ACS 5-year 2006-2010</title>
                <onlink>https://gisrevprxy.seattle.gov/arcgis/rest/services/CENSUS_EXT/TRACT_ACS_5Y10_TOP20/MapServer/1</onlink>
                <onlink>http://seattlecitygis.maps.arcgis.com/home/item.html?id=ddd48c8bf8fa47e79ceaa39b816864db</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>Data from:  American Community Survey, 5-year Series 2006-2010King County, Washington census tracts with American Community Survey data derived from the U.S. Census Bureau's demographic profiles (DP02-DP05).  The geo service includes over 50 attributes of the most frequently requested data.Tracts have been coded as being within the City of Seattle as well as assigned to neighborhood groups called &amp;quot;Community Reporting Areas&amp;quot;. These areas were created after the 2000 census to provide geographically consistent neighborhoods through time for reporting U.S. Census Bureau data. This is not an attempt to identify neighborhood boundaries as defined by neighborhoods themselves.Please see the item page for the source map service for more information.</abstract>
            <purpose>This layer shows the census tract boundaries for King County, Washington with associated demographic data. These are 2006-2010 5-year American Community Survey (ACS) estimates of basic population and housing attributes shown by 2010 census tract.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>tracts</themekey>
                <themekey>ACS</themekey>
                <themekey>Planning</themekey>
                <themekey>demographics</themekey>
                <themekey>census</themekey>
                <themekey>ACS5Y10</themekey>
                <themekey>GIS</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>PDDL | This item is meant for public access and use. The City of Seattle makes no representation or warranty as to its accuracy. Important | The City of Seattle has created this service for our GIS Open Data website. We do reserve the right to alter, suspend, re-host, or retire this service at any time and without notice. GIS staff will provide notification of changes via the Comments RSS capability in ArcGIS Online.The City of Seattle makes no representation or warranty as to its accuracy, and in particular, its accuracy as to labeling, dimensions, contours, property boundaries, or placement or location of any map feature thereof.</useconst>
        <datacred>City of Seattle, Office of Planning and
Community Development</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20190802</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
